mjd.tv 2013-03-15

# Privacy Policy | MJD.tv

Playernet.tv and its network of sites (the “Site” or “we”) have adopted this Privacy Policy because we are committed to protecting your privacy. The following Privacy Policy is only in effect for the Web pages, newsletters, discussion lists and opt-in announcement lists owned and operated by the Site. 

By using the Site you agree to this Privacy Policy. 

This Privacy Policy is effective as of August 10, 2010.

If you choose to visit the Site, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and the Site’s Terms of Use including limitations on damages, jurisdiction of disputes and application of the law of the State of New York.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us at [privacy@PLAYERNET.TV](mailto:privacy@PLAYERNET.TV) or write to us at: 

Big Bang, LLC.  
90 West St.  
Suite 6C  
New York, NY 10006

### The Information We Collect and How We Use It

**The Information You Provide To Us**  
In order for you to access certain free services that we offer via the Site, we may require you to provide us with certain information that personally identifies you. Such information may include your name, address, email address and telephone number. This information may also be used by us to verify your identity, notify you of related products and services offered via the Site and/or to conduct a survey. If you give your permission during the account registration process, we may share your contact information with our business partners or other companies so that they may send you promotional materials but we will not share or sell your personally identifiable information to third parties for any purpose without your express permission. Except as stated above, we will not send you an email or mailing that you have not agreed to receive.

**Accessing the Site**  
When you request a page within the Site, our Web servers automatically recognize your domain name and IP address. The domain name and IP address reveal nothing personal about you other than the IP address from which you have accessed the Site. We may provide this information to other companies and individuals to perform functions on behalf the Site. This information may be used to examine our traffic in aggregate and to investigate misuse of the Site, its users or to cooperate with law enforcement.

**Cookies**  
From time to time, the Site or its advertisers may send a "cookie" to your computer. A cookie is a small piece of data that is sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other Web sites. Cookies do not damage your system. We use cookies to identify which areas of the Site you have visited or customized, so the next time you visit those pages they may be readily accessible. Along with our advertisers, we may also use cookies to ascertain how many times you've seen an advertisement and to better personalize the content, banners, and promotions that you see on our site. You can choose whether to accept cookies by changing the settings of your browser. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies, or allow your browser to show you when a cookie is being sent. If you choose not to accept these cookies, your experience at our Site and other Web sites may be diminished and some features may not work as intended. 

**User Submitted Information**  
Any personal information or content that you voluntarily disclose online (on discussion boards, uploaded videos or pictures, in messages, chat areas, etc.) may become publicly available and can be collected and used by others. In addition, we may use this information and/or redistribute this information through the Internet and other media channels affiliated with this Site. 

**Choices for Personal Information**  
When you sign up for a particular service that requires registration, we ask you to provide personal information. If we use this information in a manner different than the purpose for which it was collected, then we will ask for your consent prior to such use. We will not collect or use your personal information for purposes other than those described in this Privacy Policy, unless we have obtained your prior consent.

**Information Sharing**  
We will disclose personal information and/or an IP address, when required by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:

Conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on us,  
Protect and defend the rights or property of the Site, or visitors to the Site and related properties,  
Identify persons who may be violating the law, the Site’s Terms of Use, the rights of third parties, or otherwise misusing the Site or its related properties,  
Cooperate with the investigations of purported unlawful activities.

In addition, we reserve the right to transfer all such information (i.e., either personally identifiable or not) in connection with the sale of all or part of our capital stock or assets.

**In the Event of Merger, Sale, or Bankruptcy.**  
In the event that the Site is acquired by or merged with a third party entity, we reserve the right, in any of these circumstances, to transfer or assign the information we have collected from our Users as part of such merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control. In the unlikely event of our bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, or the application of laws or equitable principles affecting creditors' rights generally, we may not be able to control how your personal information is treated, transferred, or used. 

**Other Sites**  
We may allow third parties to advertise on the Site. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the business and privacy practices of these other sites. We encourage you to be aware of this when you leave the Site and to read the legal notices and privacy policies of each and every website you visit.

**Security Measures**  
We have reasonable security measures in place and technologies to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of your information under our control but we cannot assure that your personally identifiable information or non-personally identifiable information will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Policy. Furthermore, we are not responsible for any breach of security or for any actions of any third parties that receive the information. 

**Children’s Online Protection Act**  
The Site serves general users of the World Wide Web. We support and comply with the Children’s Online Protection Act (COPPA) and we do not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13, nor do we share such information with third parties. Children under the age of 18 may use the Site only with the involvement of a parent or guardian.

**Accessing and updating personal information**  
We make good faith efforts to provide you with access to your personal information and either to correct this data if it is inaccurate or to delete such data at your request if it is not otherwise required to be retained by law or for legitimate business purposes. We will ask that you identify yourself and the information requested to be accessed, corrected or removed before processing such requests, and we may decline to process requests that require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of others, or would be extremely impractical , or for which access is not otherwise required. In any case where we provide information access and correction, we perform this service free of charge, except if doing so would require a disproportionate effort. The initial procedure to access, correct or delete your personal information is contact: [privacy@playernet.tv](mailto:privacy@playernet.tv). 

**Notification of Changes to the Privacy Policy**  
If we decide to change this Privacy Policy, we will post these changes on our Homepage or provide other notification of our revised Privacy Policy so you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and when we disclose it. We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. Your continued use of the Site constitutes your acceptance to the new Privacy Policy. If we decide to materially or substantively changes Privacy Policy (i.e,, change our treatment of information collected at this site), we will notify you by posting a clear and conspicuous notice of these changes on our website and in this Privacy Policy. If you would like to be notified by email if and when material changes are made to this Privacy Policy, please opt in to receiving such email notifications by contacting us at [privacy@playernet.tv](mailto:privacy@playernet.tv).
